Guide to the Houston Women's Caucus for Art Records
University of Houston Libraries
Houston Women's Caucus for Art Records
1972-2004
1985-2000
1999-001
Women's Caucus for Art. Houston Chapter
14.00 Linear Feet
Special Collections, University of Houston Libraries
The papers for the Houston Women’s Caucus for Art (HWCA) span from its founding in 1978 to 2004. Some items, however, pre-date this period. The largest portion of the records is devoted to photos and to art exhibitions sponsored by the Caucus. The next largest portion includes newsletters, grant applications and fundraising, financial records, and conferences. The remainder of the collection is devoted to information pertaining to the business of the Caucus, membership, and the visual arts in Houston.
Historical Note:
The surge of woman-centered activity that came in the wake of the 1977 National Women’s Conference inspired women in Houston’s artistic community to bind together and form their own chapter of the Women’s Caucus for Art. The National Women’s Caucus for Art had grown out of a discussion on gender at an art conference in San Francisco, California in 1972. The national organization’s stated purpose was “to win parity in the valuation of works by women; to create new opportunities for women to document, produce and exhibit works, and to assemble for the exchange of ideas, experience and constructive criticism.” On January 10, 1978, the Houston Women’s Caucus for Art expanded that mission to Houston and held its first organizational meeting. In 1980, the state of Texas recognized the group as a non-profit organization.
Meetings were held monthly, and membership quickly expanded. Members elected a board of directors, or executive board. The positions in this board have varied over the years, but consisted of a president, program coordinator, secretary, treasurer, exhibition coordinator, publicity coordinator, membership coordinator, newsletter editor, and special events coordinator in 1997. The board makes all of the major decisions for the organization; however, officers welcome input from a community advisory board and all members.
While the Caucus first met in the household of one of its members, the organization soon realized the need for a larger meeting space. Preferably, this space should have a gallery in which members could hold exhibitions. To obtain this, the Caucus joined other Montrose area organizations in the Neartown Association. This neighborhood community group helped to preserve and restore an old Montrose fire station at 1413 Westheimer, which became the meeting and exhibition hall for all groups. By 1983, the Caucus proved to be the most frequent user of the facility, and signed a long-term lease. In 1998, Harris County purchased the Firehouse and the Caucus continued to sublet its space as a gallery for experimental, up and coming, and member artists until 1999. During 1999, the county decided to use the entire building as office space, and so the Caucus relocated to 3015 Richmond, Suite 270, in the Upper Kirby Building. The Caucus has an office and a large meeting room available, but presently does not have a space to use as a gallery.
The Caucus has remained true to its purposes in over three decades of its existence. The group sponsors local artists through individual, group, and member shows. The organization has also helped to bring many artists of national renown and controversy to Houston, such as Matuschka, Judy Chicago, and Karen Finley. Not only has the Caucus shown a commitment to artistic expression, but it has also shown a commitment to feminist activism. Exhibitions have included artwork by survivors of domestic violence and art promoting awareness of breast cancer. Furthermore, the very existence of the HWCA has allowed many women an exhibition space that would otherwise be denied to them due to gender and racial discrimination in the art world.
Source:
www.artwomenhouston.org
Note Author: Leigh Fought, June 1999
Access Terms
This Collection is indexed under the following controlled access subject terms.
Corporate Name:
Women's Caucus for Art. Houston Chapter
Genre/Form of Material:
Administrative records; Brochures; Bylaws (administrative records); Correspondence; Newsletters; Photographs
Topical Term:
Art -- Texas -- Houston; Artists -- Texas -- Houston; Feminism and art; Nonprofit organizations -- Texas -- Houston; Women -- Societies and clubs -- Texas -- Houston; Women artists -- Texas -- Houston
Acquisition Information:
Donated by Houston Women's Caucus for Art, 1999. Additional materials were acquired in 2008 as part of a donation by Houston Women's Caucus for Art.
Conditions Governing Access:
Open for research.
Related Materials:
Houston Gorilla Girls Records http://archon.lib.uh.edu/index.php?p=collections/controlcard&id=468
Scope and Contents
The papers for the Houston Women’s Caucus for Art (HWCA) span from its founding in 1978 to 2004. Some items, however, pre-date this period. The largest portion of the records is devoted to photos and to art exhibitions sponsored by the Caucus. The next largest portion includes newsletters, grant applications and fundraising, financial records, and conferences. The remainder of the collection is devoted to information pertaining to the business of the Caucus, membership, and the visual arts in Houston. Many of the items located in this collection do not specifically deal with the HWCA. Some are more general art news, activism, arts organizations, or other chapters of the National Women’s Caucus for Art. These materials have been retained in order to give researchers a sense of the networking, interests, and activities of the Caucus beyond the city of Houston.
The collection has fifteen series: Administration; Firehouse Gallery; Newsletters; Shows; Events; Fundraising; Members; Finances; Conferences; Photos; Clippings; General Visual Arts; Posters; Lectures, Papers and Speeches; and Printed Materials. The original arrangement varied according to year. Generally, previous record keepers tended to organize the documents around fundraising, particularly grant applications, and around art shows sponsored by the Caucus. This current organization was imposed by the archivist, and follows a topical arrangement.
Detailed List of Contents
- Administration, 1978-2000
  Scope and Contents
  Information on the formation and business operation of the Houston Women’s Caucus for Art from 1978 to 2000 lies in the Administration series. This series contains six sub-series: Documentation, Correspondence, Board, Meetings, Mode, and Office. The Documentation sub-series includes such official organizational information as the by-laws, articles of incorporation, mission statement, various guidelines, and the official history of the HWCA. The Correspondence sub-series contains all general correspondence to HWCA. Letters referring to specific events or grants were kept in those categories. The Board sub-series includes rosters of the officers for the Community Advisory board and the Executive Board, as well as descriptions of board positions. This sub-series also contains two folders, President (Joy Mullet), and Chapter Representative, that duplicate most of the information found throughout the collection. These two folders have been kept intact, as they were found in the original order of the collection, in order to give researchers insight into the activity of a president and chapter representative through the course of their tenure. The Meetings sub-series contains the outline for the original meeting of the HWCA, and the announcements, agenda, and minutes for subsequent meetings. This set is incomplete. The MODE sub-series contains the documentation of activities to identify and address organizational deficiencies under the Management Assistance and Organizational Development Enterprise (MODE) and Intensive Service Program (ISP) offered through the Cultural Arts Council of Houston/Harris County. The Office sub-series includes media mailing lists, notes scribbled on scrap paper, information of office supplies and printers, and the address for the HWCA web site.
  - Documentation
    - Mission Statement, approximately 1980-1999 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - History, 1982-1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - By-laws, 1979-2000 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Chapter Organization Guidelines, approximately 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Affirmative Action Policy, 1988, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Women's Business Enterprises Certification, 1987-1989 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Ethics Guidelines, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence
    - 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - 1999-2001 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Email, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Email, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Email, 2000-2001 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Board
    - Community Advisory Board, 1980-1997 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Executive Board, 1981-1997 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - President, 1981, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - President (Joy Mullet), January-June 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - President, 1996-2002 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Chapter Representative, 1992-1993 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Position Descriptions, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Committees, 1979-2000 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Survey, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Meetings
    - Suggested Procedures, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - 1978-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - 1990-1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - 1997-February 1998 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - July 1998-June 1999 (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - July 1999-June 2000 (Box 1, Folder 32)
    - July 2000-June 2001 (Box 1, Folder 33)
    - National, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 34)
    - National, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 35)
    - National, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 36)
    - National, 1999-2000 (Box 1, Folder 37)
    - National - Chapter Development Handbook, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - National - Summer Board Meeting and Events, July 7-9, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Board, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Board, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Board, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Board, 1995-1997 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Board, 1999-2000 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Management Assistance and Organizational Development Enterprise (MODE)
    - Application, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Assessment and Workplan, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Monthly Reports, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Outline of Activities, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Procedures and Guidelines, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Surveys, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, 1999-2000 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Office
    - Brochures, approximately 1980-1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - “Caucus” Online Board Room, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Gallery and Office Space Agreements, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Logo Research, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Media Mailing Lists, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Media Mailing Lists, undated (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, undated (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Office Supply Catalogs, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Printing Sources, 1995-1997 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Shipping/Mailing Information, 1981, 1987, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Stationery, approximately 1980-1998 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Volunteers, 1998-2000 (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Web Site, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Firehouse Gallery, 1980-1999
  The HWCA held exhibitions and meetings in the old Firehouse building on Westheimer Road until 1999. This series contains information relating to that building from its renovation as a community center in 1980, through the HWCA use and upkeep of the facility until 1999. The series is organized alphabetically by subject.
  - Alarm System, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Expenses, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Floor Plans, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Gallery Agreements, 1982-1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Gallery Sitters, 1992-1994 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - History, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Insurance, 1982-1986, 1996-1997 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Lease Agreement, 1986, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Neartown Association, 1984-1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Parking, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Renovation, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Sign, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Use, 1980-1995 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Newsletters, 1978-2003
  The Newsletters series spans the years 1978 to 2003. They are divided into four sub-series: Houston, Other Chapters, Regional, and National. The National newsletter changed titles several times, from simply Newsletter, to Hue Points, to Update, Member News, and Artlines. An incomplete set of these can be found in the National sub-series. Researchers wishing to find a full set of National newsletters should refer to the National Women’s Caucus for Art archives in New Jersey. The Regional sub-series contains only one folder, and is not specific to any region. The Other Chapters sub-series contains newsletters for various WCA chapters throughout the nation. This sub-series is arranged alphabetically according to state, then according to chapter within that state. None of the sets of these newsletters are complete, and researchers should refer to those individual chapters for more information. Although the National, Regional, and Chapter sub-series do not contain all of the newsletters for those organizations, they have been retained in this collection in order for researchers to ascertain the interaction of the HWCA with their sister organizations throughout the nation. The Houston sub-series contains an incomplete set of newsletters for the HWCA, arranged chronologically. This set is almost complete, missing most of 1986, 1987, 1989, and 1990.
  - Houston
    - 1978-1980 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - 1983-1984 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - 1989-1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - 1991-1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - 1996-1998 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - 1999-2003 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Other Chapters
    - Arizona, California, 1982-2002 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Colorado, Connecticut, 1992-1998 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Florida, 1983-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Illinois, Indiana, Iowa, 1989-1999 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Louisiana, Massachusetts, Minnesota, Missouri, 1979-1999 (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Nebraska, New Hampshire, New Jersey, New Mexico, New York, 1983-2002 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Ohio, Oregon, Pennsylvania/New Jersey/Delaware, 1979-1998 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Texas, 1992-1994 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Vermont, Virginia, 1982-1994 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Washington, Washington, D.C., Wisconsin, 1979-2001 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Southern New Mexico, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Southwest Region, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Various Chapter Materials, 1989-1990 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Regional
    - 1990-1994, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - National
    - 1978-1979 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Newsletter, 1980-1981 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Hue Points, 1982, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Update, 1986-1989 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Update, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Update, 1993-1995 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Update, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Member News, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Email Bulletin, 1999-2001 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Artilines, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Member News, 1999 (Ovs box 14, Folder 1)
    - Artilines, 2000-2001 (Ovs box 14, Folder 2)
- Shows, 1981-2003
  The Shows series includes information, programs, invitations, and correspondence regarding exhibitions sponsored by the Caucus. The series covers the years 1981 through 2003, and is divided into seven sub-series: Schedule of Events, Member Show, Firehouse, Annex, Proposed, Houston Area, and Out of Town. The shows in these sub-series are arranged chronologically.
  - Schedule of Events
    - 1979-2000 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Member Show
    - 1980, March 1980 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - NOW State Convention 1980, May 16-18, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - 1981 [?], October 10-28, 1981 [?] (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - 1984, February-June 1984 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - "Self-Images", April 5-May 10, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - “Self-Images” 1985 - Loan Agreements, April 5-May 10, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Austin, TX 1989, June 4-24, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - "Revealing Ourselves" 1991, September 1991 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - "Common Denominator" 1992, September 15-October 9, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "SisterSister: Who We Are" 1994, September 9-October 15, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "SisterSister: Who We Are" 1994 - San Antonio, TX, January 8-28, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Power in Transition" 1995, February 1-March 31, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - "Out of the Cold" Fall 1995, September 30-October 29, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - "Personal Alchemy" 1997, September 6-October 12, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - “Hotel Houston” 1997, October 17-November 16, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - “Miniature Works” 1999, May 8-June 6, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - “Visual Interlude” 1999, October 14-November 26, 1999 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - “Celebrating the Riches of Our Diversity” 2001, February 8-March 30, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - “Flash” 2003, October 2003 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Firehouse
    - Dedication Exhibit, August 1982-May 1983 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - “A Room of One’s Own", September 11, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - "Traces", December 1983-January 1984 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - "Swamp Songs" - Clyde Connell, September 20-October 27, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - "Paper Tiger", November 2-December 1, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - "Homages in Clay" - Jose Varela, December 7, 1984-January 15, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - "Private Rites", January 22-February 23, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - "Innovative Prints", March 8-April 12, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - "Some Things Are Not What They Seem", May 21-June 22, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - "Men of the Women's Caucus", October 4-30, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - "Passageways" - Karen Hillier, November 5-27, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - “Creatures” - Bobbye Bennett, December 3, 1985-January 17, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - “Entrance II” - Patricia Carr Morgan, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - "The Neverending Story", January 1986 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - "Contemporary Women in Documentary Photography", March 1-29, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - "Herstory: Black Women Photographers", March 4-25, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - "At Twelve" - Sally Mann, February 10-March 10, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - "Boxworks: Ancestors Known and Unknown", May 7-June 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - "Wallpaper" - Annette Lawrence, October 11-November 10, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - "Desperately Seeking...", April 14-18, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Guest books, 1992-1996 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - "Trail of Tears", January 10-February 1, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - "Ex-Officio", February 6-March 7, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - "Self-Discovery of Women" - Debra Reub, March 13-April 1, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - "Women Taking a Stand", August 1992 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - "From Within Walls", October 23-November 14, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - "Goddesses, Witches, and Saints", December 1992-January 1993 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - "Conception, Pre-Conception", February 27-March 26, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - “Taking a Bite of the Apple", April 10-May 15, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - “Wild Women, Art Savage", September 10-October 2, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - "Untold Stories", November 12-December 31, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - "Perceptions of Men", January 21-February 26, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - "Women and Aging", March 12-April 19, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - "Ecofeminism", April 15-May 20, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - "Dogs Bark but the Caravan Moves On", May-June 1994 (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - "Social Reflections" - Elisa Alvarado, July 29-August 27, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - "Out of the Sky" - Anne Noggle, November 12-December 10, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - "A Conversation Piece", January 14-February 10, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - "Compañeras", February 17-March 31, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - "Healing Works", April 11-May 21, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - "Landscapes of the Mind" - Ann Webb, June 10-July 9, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - "Thought and Choice" - Laurie Waller, July 15-August 12, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - "Primitive Streak", August 19-September 16, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - "Serial Imagery", November 11-25, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Artgirls of the West, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 58)
    - Artgirls of the West - Marilyn Bendell, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Artgirls of the West - B. J. Billups, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Artgirls of the West - Beverly Carrick, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - Artgirls of the West - Louise DeMore, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 62)
    - Artgirls of the West - B. R. Gates, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 63)
    - Artgirls of the West - Catherine Gill, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 64)
    - Artgirls of the West - Janice Yow Hines, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 65)
    - Artgirls of the West - DeAnne Limley, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 66)
    - Artgirls of the West - Martha Saudek, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 67)
    - Artgirls of the West - Sherry Blanchard Stewart, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 68)
    - Artgirls of the West - artists, January 6-February 25, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 69)
    - "1/2 of 1/2 of 1/2" - Matuschka, March 1-April 22, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 70)
    - "Salon des Oeuvres Refuses", May 5-June 2, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - “A Journey Into Healing” - Mary Erbert, June 8- July 9, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - "Elements of Imagination" - Lucy Wiley, July 13-August 4, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - "Altars as Art", September 21-November 16, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - "Luscious Show", January 11-February 28, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - "Women and Cleaning", July 12-August 16, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - "The Circle" - the Artists' Way, June 7-July 5, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - “Slip and Slide", 1997, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - “Photo Realism", January 20-February 28, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - “Luminous Code", 1998 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous, 1991-1997 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Artful Objects, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Taking a Stand!, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Three City Women’s Caucus Travelling Art Show, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Annex
    - "Creative Communities, Making Friends", September 23-November 3, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - "Aubrey McCaskell's Place", December 18, 1995-February 28, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Various Materials, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Proposed
    - 1982-1999 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Houston Area
    - "The Exchange: AH-HA", January 23-February 13, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - "Women Sculptors' Drawings", 1982 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - "Showdown", November 4-30, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Karen Finley, October 27-28, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Traveling Slide Exhibition, Spring 1990 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - "Mail Art", February 10-March 3, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Canary Project, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Canary Project - "Banners Project", 1997-2000 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Canary Project - Database of Possible Donors, 1996-1999 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Canary Project - Finances, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Canary Project - Unit Sponsor - Alamo Breast Cancer Foundation and Coalition (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Canary Project - Unit Sponsor - Houston Ladies’ Tennis Association (Box 5, Folder 26)